My role is serving corporate clients every single day
I have to finish by this Wednesday no delay
The meeting is on Friday so the pressure's getting high
It's such a demanding job I gotta sit and sigh
It's very boring so I'll quit and find a brand new space
I'm searching for something to escape this relentless pace
I'm finding that it's getting old and I am truly scared
He's gonna be a manager but I am unprepared
Gotta give it a try! Gotta give it a try!
I'm gonna break these heavy chains and fly!
I get to choose my very own way today!
I've got nothing left to lose so don't you make me stay!
I'm freelance now which means that I am completely free
I could be called to any job just you wait and see
What that means is I write my own rules every single day
No more working with those corporate fools who stand in my way
It's very boring so I'll quit and find a brand new space
I'm searching for something to escape this relentless pace
I'm finding that it's getting old and I am truly scared
He's gonna be a manager but I am unprepared
Gotta give it a try! Gotta give it a try!
I'm gonna break these heavy chains and fly!
I get to choose my very own way today!
I've got nothing left to lose so don't you make me stay!
I've worked for this firm almost my whole career it's true
It's been a bit stressful with too many things to do
But I'm ready for a change the time to act is finally here
You should do what you want and conquer every single fear
Gotta give it a try! Gotta give it a try!
I'm gonna break these heavy chains and fly!
I get to choose my very own way today!
I've got nothing left to lose so don't you make me stay!
Gotta give it a try! Gotta give it a try!
I'm gonna go, I'm finding that I'm finally free!
Yeah! This is my life now! (Go!)